{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Lancer\"?",
	"Answer": "Alex"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Professor\"?",
	"Answer": "Alfred"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Iron Princess\"?",
	"Answer": "Angela"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Conqueror of Battlefield\"?",
	"Answer": "Aran"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Artificial Angel\"?",
	"Answer": "Azrael"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Witch\"?",
	"Answer": "Banshee"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Reinforced Human\"?",
	"Answer": "Bearman"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Healer\"?",
	"Answer": "Belle"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Big Shot\"?",
	"Answer": "Carrot"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Wildcat\"?",
	"Answer": "Cat Sidhe"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Dragon\"?",
	"Answer": "Celestial"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Magician\"?",
	"Answer": "Chenny"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"White Knight\"?",
	"Answer": "Chris"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Succubus\"?",
	"Answer": "Cleo"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Magician\"?",
	"Answer": "Deborah"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Tyrant\"?",
	"Answer": "Deimos"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Nouveau Riche\"?",
	"Answer": "Dolores"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Resistance\"?",
	"Answer": "Dominique"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Fonea Queen\"?",
	"Answer": "Elektra"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Dragon Master\"?",
	"Answer": "Evan"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Forgotten Hero\"?",
	"Answer": "Eunwol"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Butler\"?",
	"Answer": "Frankenstein"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Combat Ranger\"?",
	"Answer": "Fruel"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Drug Master\"?",
	"Answer": "Gillan"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Aide\"?",
	"Answer": "Hella"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Killing Machine\"?",
	"Answer": "Henry"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Black Cat\"?",
	"Answer": "Ian"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Werewolf\"?",
	"Answer": "Jack"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Cowgirl\"?",
	"Answer": "Jenny"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Mercenary Captain\"?",
	"Answer": "Jin"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Hero\"?",
	"Answer": "Jin Kisaragi"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Hero\"?",
	"Answer": "Kai"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Android\"?",
	"Answer": "Kitty"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Archmage\"?",
	"Answer": "Klein"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Orc Warrior\"?",
	"Answer": "Krut"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Golem\"?",
	"Answer": "Lance"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Psychokinetic\"?",
	"Answer": "Lee"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Diva\"?",
	"Answer": "Lena"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Wild Boy\"?",
	"Answer": "Lilid"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Maid\"?",
	"Answer": "Lily"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Zombie\"?",
	"Answer": "Lucas"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Guardian of Light\"?",
	"Answer": "Luminous"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Bard\"?",
	"Answer": "Mas"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Elf Queen\"?",
	"Answer": "Mercedes"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Black Wizard\"?",
	"Answer": "Moa"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"White Rabbit\"?",
	"Answer": "Momo"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Exorcist\"?",
	"Answer": "Mu"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Pyromaniac\"?",
	"Answer": "Muang"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Werewolf\"?",
	"Answer": "Muzaka"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Healer\"?",
	"Answer": "Nirvana"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Successor\"?",
	"Answer": "Noel"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Vampire\"?",
	"Answer": "Nox"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Phantom Thief\"?",
	"Answer": "Persona"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Thief\"?",
	"Answer": "Phantom"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Phoenix\"?",
	"Answer": "Poni"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Vampire\"?",
	"Answer": "Rachel"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"General\"?",
	"Answer": "Raboff"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Gunner\"?",
	"Answer": "Rage"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Reaper\"?",
	"Answer": "Ragna"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Noblesse\"?",
	"Answer": "Raizel"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Lord\"?",
	"Answer": "Raskreia"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Wolf Hunter\"?",
	"Answer": "Reina"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Reaper\"?",
	"Answer": "Seira"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Dryad\"?",
	"Answer": "Serendi"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Conqueror of Battlefield\"?",
	"Answer": "Aran"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Magic Knight\"?",
	"Answer": "Serphina"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Pirate\"?",
	"Answer": "Shark"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Little Angel\"?",
	"Answer": "Shu-Shu"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Black Bride\"?",
	"Answer": "Sione"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Ninja\"?",
	"Answer": "Sonic Boom"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Witch\"?",
	"Answer": "Spooky"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Orc Warrior\"?",
	"Answer": "Sraka"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Kung Fu Girl\"?",
	"Answer": "Tao"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Wanderer\"?",
	"Answer": "Unknown"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Soul Gear\"?",
	"Answer": "Valkyrie"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Magician\"?",
	"Answer": "Yekaterina"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Assassin\"?",
	"Answer": "Zero"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Dragon\"?",
	"Answer": "Thanatos"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Escort\"?",
	"Answer": "Ildo"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Painter\"?",
	"Answer": "Taehwa"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Vermillion Bird\"?",
	"Answer": "Hongyeom"
},{
	"Question": "Which hero has the title of \"Fortune-teller\"?",
	"Answer": "Ryeogang"
},